{
    "subject": "Noboru_Iguchi",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Oira_Sukeban",
    "human_readable": "Noboru Iguchi created Oira Sukeban.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9351600408554077,
            "question": "Is Noboru Iguchi known for creating other works besides 'Oira Sukeban'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8089220523834229,
            "question": "Who created the work 'Oira Sukeban'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7577973008155823,
            "question": "When was 'Oira Sukeban' created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.649976372718811,
            "question": "What is the title of the work created by Noboru Iguchi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5230045318603516,
            "question": "What is the genre of 'Oira Sukeban'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4999500513076782,
            "question": "Who are some of the main characters in 'Oira Sukeban'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43037599325180054,
            "question": "How has 'Oira Sukeban' been received by audiences and critics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4219125211238861,
            "question": "What type of creative work is 'Oira Sukeban'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39948007464408875,
            "question": "Are there any adaptations of 'Oira Sukeban' in other media?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38742128014564514,
            "question": "What themes does 'Oira Sukeban' explore?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Noboru Iguchi created Oira Sukeban.",
            "html": "yago_17984_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any adaptations of 'Oira Sukeban' in other media?",
            "html": "yago_17984_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of creative work is 'Oira Sukeban'?",
            "html": "yago_17984_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has 'Oira Sukeban' been received by audiences and critics?",
            "html": "yago_17984_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17984_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17984_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17984_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17984_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17984_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17984_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17984_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17984_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17984_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17984_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided supports the statement that Noboru Iguchi created or directed \"Oira Sukeban\" as it explicitly mentions in one of the documents: \"Iguchi also wrote and directed the February 2006 film Sukeban Boy or Oira Sukeban (\u304a\u3044\u3089\u5973\u86ee \u30b9\u30b1\u30d0\u30f3, Oira sukeban) with AV star Asami.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}